{
    "subject": "resource/James_Dyrenforth",
    "predicate": "ontology/abstract",
    "object": "James Dyrenforth (31 January 1895 \u2013 26 December 1973) was an American actor and songwriter. Dyrenforth appeared in A Night to Remember (1958), Fiend Without a Face (1958), and Lolita, and co-wrote \"A Garden in the Rain\", a song which was covered by Frank Sinatra and Sarah Vaughan, among others.",
    "human_readable": "James Dyrenforth's abstract is James Dyrenforth (31 January 1895 \u2013 26 December 1973) was an American actor and songwriter. He appeared in A Night to Remember (1958), Fiend Without a Face (1958), and Lolita, and co-wrote 'A Garden in the Rain', a song which was covered by Frank Sinatra and Sarah Vaughan, among others.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8986414670944214,
            "question": "Was James Dyrenforth American?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8704211115837097,
            "question": "What were some of the movies that James Dyrenforth appeared in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8570345640182495,
            "question": "What song did James Dyrenforth co-write?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8307085037231445,
            "question": "When was James Dyrenforth born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8282629251480103,
            "question": "Name one movie that James Dyrenforth starred in."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7801327109336853,
            "question": "What profession was James Dyrenforth known for besides acting?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7364530563354492,
            "question": "What year did James Dyrenforth die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6772449612617493,
            "question": "What decade did James Dyrenforth die in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6074472665786743,
            "question": "Which famous singers covered 'A Garden in the Rain'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2767198383808136,
            "question": "What is another word for 'songwriter'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=James Dyrenforth's abstract is James Dyrenforth (31 January 1895 \u2013 26 December 1973) was an American actor and songwriter. He appeared in A Night to Remember (1958), Fiend Without a Face (1958), and Lolita, and co-wrote 'A Garden in the Rain', a song which was covered by Frank Sinatra and Sarah Vaughan, among others.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1490_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which famous singers covered 'A Garden in the Rain'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1490_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What decade did James Dyrenforth die in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1490_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year did James Dyrenforth die?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1490_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1490_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1490_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1490_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1490_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1490_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1490_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1490_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1490_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1490_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1490_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\nThe provided text mentions James Dyrenforth as an actor and songwriter, but it doesn't state that his abstract is the given biographical information.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe provided documents mention that James Dyrenforth was an actor who appeared in several films including \"A Night to Remember\" (1958), \"Floods of Fear\" (1958), and \"Lolita\" (1961). Additionally, it is noted that he was a songwriter and co-wrote the song \"A Garden In The Rain.\" This information supports the given abstract."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Information provided states his acting career spanned from 1958 to 2015, contradicting a death in 1973.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}